Guide to the Elizabeth Robins Papers 1803-1963 MSS 002
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Legal and Financial Records
  - Legal Size Material
    - Royalty Statements 1927 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Financial Records--Chinsegut 1905-1913, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Financial Records--miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Series XI: Scrapbooks
  The scrapbooks are arranged chronologically by the first date in each. The scrapbooks contain press clippings gathered together into volumes by either Elizabeth Robins or her husband, George Richmond Parks. It does not appear that negative reviews were censored.
  - Subseries A: Elizabeth Robins, 1874-1904
    Elizabeth Robins’ scrapbooks contain a wide variety of material, including, but not limited to, printed poems of her two aunts, anecdotes, articles on historical and theological interests, wedding invitations, favorite etchings, playbills, theatre reviews, letters and mentions of friends and relations.
    - Bessie Robins from Papa, Putnam, Ohio 1874-1885 (Scrapbook 1)
    - "Weddings and etc" 1874-1883 (Scrapbook 2)
    - "To Bessie with much love from Cousin Lizzie Bodine, Christmas 1875" 1875 (Scrapbook 3)
      Color picture book.
    - Bedford, Mass. '83" 1883 (Scrapbook 4)
      Etching prints of personalities.
    - Criticisms and Notices of Plays 1883-1890 (Scrapbook 5)
    - "Elizabeth Robins Parks, July 1886, 'Good Ones'" 1885/1886 (Scrapbook 6)
      Clippings, calling cards, etc.
    - Unbound Scrapbook 1891-1893 (Scrapbook 7)
      Mainly Hedda Gabler and The Master Builder; clippings; some posters.
    - C.E. Raimond's Scrapbook 1894, 1893-1895, 1894 -1896 (Scrapbook 8)
      Reviews of The Lucky Sixpence in The New Review (1893), George Mandeville's Husband (1894), and The New Moon (1895).
    - "Fund. Press Notices. 'Little Eyolf' '96" 1896 (Scrapbook 9)
      Subscription campaign for Little Eyolf and Mariana; criticisms and notices for Little Eyolf and John Gabriel Borkman.
    - "Admiral Guinea, Honesty Press Cuttings" 1897 (Scrapbook 10)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 4, Folders 11-12.
    - General Clippings 1898-1899 (Scrapbook 11)
      Reviews of Thackeray, Shaw, Swinburne, etc.; some clippings from Louisville Courier Journal, e.g. on death of Lloyd Tevis; C.E. Raimond letter.
    - The Open Question 1898-1899 (Scrapbook 12)
      Clippings; letters; telegrams; letters from various people to William Heinemann.
    - The Magnetic North 1904 (Scrapbook 13)
  - Subseries B: George Richmond Parks, 1871-1883
    George Richmond Parks kept four scrapbooks, two of which contain only playbills.
    - Playbills 1871-1886 (Scrapbook 1)
    - Playbills 1877-1886 (Scrapbook 2)
    - "George R. Parks" 1879-1883 (Scrapbook 3)
      Criticisms, notices, poems, quotes, menus, and articles of interest from several American newspapers.
    - "Criticisms and Notices 1883 George R. Parks, 1883" (Scrapbook 4)
      Indexed; mainly Boston newspapers.
- Series XII: Printed Materials
  Series XII contains a wide variety of materials, including theater programs, posters, proofs (galleys and page), magazines, newspaper clippings, brochures, pamphlets, and maps.
  - Subseries A: Proofs of Elizabeth Robins' Literary Productions
    Subseries A consists of annotated page proofs and galleys of many of Robins’ works. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Ancilla's Share, marked proof (Chapters 1-14) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Ancilla's Share, marked proof (Chapters 15-30) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bolt Seventeen (1919), n.d. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Bolt Seventeen (Fortnightly, January 1920) (Box 2, Folder 3A)
    - Come and Find Me, page proofs (1907) (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Came and Find Me, galleys (1907)--see Oversize Material, Box 2, Folder 6.
    - Elizabeth Robins on Sir Herbert Austin (1933) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Ibsen and the Actress, page proofs (1928) (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - The Main Peace Asset (Box 2, Folder 7)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 9, Folder 6.
    - Mills of the Gods, page proofs, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Pleasure Mining, page proofs, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Theatre and Friendship, page proofs (1932) (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Theatre and Friendship, galleys--see Oversize Material, Box 2, Folder 8.
    - Theatre and Friendship, page proofs (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
    - Time is Whispering, page proofs, (pages 1-176) (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Time is Whispering, page proofs, (pages 177-320) (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Time is Whispering, galleys--see also Oversize Material, Box 9, Folder 4.
    - Where are You Going To?, page proofs (1912) (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Why?, page proofs (1910), 1912 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Woman Comes of Age (Box 3, Folder 17)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 2, Folder 10.
    - The Woman Juror (to the editor of The Morning Post) (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Woman's Secret, page proofs (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Subseries B: Publications by Elizabeth Robins
    Subseries B consists primarily of short stories and articles. These publications are arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Below the Salt (The New Review, No. 86, July 1896, pp. 1 -17) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Confessions of a Cruel Mistress (Chapman's Magazine of Fiction, No. 4, Vol. 1, August 1895, pp. 361-379) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Dr. Flora Murray, Reminiscences Of Her War Work (The Observer, August 5, 1923) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Gustus Frederick (The New Review, No. 70, March 1895, pp 270 - 281) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Ibsen and the Actress (London: Hogarth Press, 1928) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Letter to the editor of "The Times." Reprinted as broadside by Ministry of Health, Women's Consultative Council, March 20. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Lost and Found, A Story (Harpers Magazine, September 1915, pp 500 - 511) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - A Lucky Sixpence (The New Review, January 1894, pp 105 -126) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - My Little Sister (McClure's Magazine, December 1912, pp 121- 145) (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Some Personal Opinions On the National Theatre. Miss Elizabeth Robins (Drama, December 1929, p. 41) (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Stretcher-Bearing for Women (The Daily Mall, August 18, 1915) (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - What Can I Do?: The Lady Chichester Hospital for Women and Children (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Woman's Place in the New Order. Purpose of Militancy (to the editor of the Times, printed May 4, 1921) (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Woman's War; a Defense of Militant Suffrage (McClure's Magazine, March 1913, pp 41 - 52) (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Women Doctors. Lord Knutsford's Charge (Sunday Times, March 12, 1922) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Subseries C: Theatre
    Subseries C includes playbills and announcements of performances, material on the New Century Theatre and publications, i.e. plays, reviews and articles. Theatrical posters have been moved to Mapcase 2.A. Playbills and announcements of Elizabeth Robins' performances are arranged alphabetically by the name of the play. There are also playbills and announcements from other performances, many with annotations that show Elizabeth Robins attended them. They are arranged alphabetically by name of play, or by name of theater if no single play is prominently mentioned. Dates of the performances are indicated infrequently. The publications consist of published plays, arranged alphabetically by title, and articles.
    - Publications - plays: Broken Hearts to London Assurance (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Publications - plays: Mariana to Proof (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Publications - plays: The Ticket-Of-Leave Man to Who's To Win Him (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Publications - reviews and articles (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Publications - reviews and articles (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Subseries D: Literary and Political Publications
    Subseries D contains an assortment of publications and a collection of book jackets. The pamphlets and articles written by a variety of authors include reviews of some of Elizabeth Robins' publications. In addition, Robins gathered a collection of articles on race relations in America, including several brochures on the Tuskegee Institute. There are several issues of Votes for Women, the Women's Social and Political Union newspaper; Equal Rights, the National Woman's Party's paper; and a run of the Woman's Journal from 1909-1910.
    - Publications re: American blacks (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Publications re: American blacks (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Tuskegee Institute, Catalogues and Brochures 1895-1904 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Tuskegee Institute, Catalogues and Brochures 1906-1907 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Publications by others (Box 6, Folder 5)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 7, Folder 4 for The Woman's Journal.
    - Publications by others (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Publications by others (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Publications by others (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Publications by others (Women and the Women's Movement) (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Book Jackets (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Subseries E: Political, Cultural and Social Events
    Subseries E consists of calling cards, broadsides and programs from Elizabeth Robins' speaking engagements, and additional programs and broadsides.
    - Broadsides and programs of Elizabeth Robins' appearances (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Calling cards (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Invitations (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Invitations (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Programs: Literary (Box 8, Folder 5A)
    - Programs: Women Institutes (Box 8, Folder 5B)
    - Programs: Panhurst Statue (Box 8, Folder 5C)
    - Programs: United States (Box 8, Folder 5D)
    - Programs: Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 5E)
    - Programs:Theatrical (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Broadsides (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - The Royal Society for the Protection of Birds (publications and clippings) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Subseries F: Backsettown
    Subseries F contains pamphlets and programs that describe Robins' Sussex home after it was converted into a rest place for women. Some are illustrated with pictures of the grounds.
    - Backsettown--programs and descriptions (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Subseries G: Putnam Female Seminary
    Subseries G includes descriptions of this boarding school attended by Elizabeth Robins and programs from performances she participated in there.
    - Putnam Female Seminary (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Subseries H: Alaska
    Subseries H includes ten maps and three folders of publications (several from the U.S. Geological Survey) on Alaska.
    - Publications (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Publications (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Publications (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Maps--see Oversize Materials, Map Drawer 2.A
  - Subseries I: Pictures
    - Pictures (Box 9, Folder 1)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 14, Folder 5.
  - Subseries J: Maps
    Subseries J contains a variety of charts and maps documenting the settlement of the Robins family in Covington, KY and the Ohio River area.
    - See Map Case 2.A
  - Subseries K: Newspaper Clippings
    Series K is made up of four boxes of unsorted newspaper clippings.
    - Unsorted clippings (Box 10)
    - Unsorted clippings (Box 11)
    - Unsorted clippings (Box 12)
    - Unsorted clippings (Box 13)
  - Subseries L: Books from Elizabeth Robins' Library
    - Creighton, Louise. Dorothy Grey (1907) (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Ibsen, Henrik. The Master Builder, 1892 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      Translated by Edmund Gosse and William Archer, 1892. ER's personal copy.
    - Ibsen, Henrik. The Master Builder, 1892 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Parish, W.D. Domesday Book in Relation to the Counts of Sussex (1886) (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - The Proverbs (New York: American Bible Society, 1867) (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Russel, Sidney. Poems (1859) (Box 14, Folder 6)
      A.k.a. Sarah Elizabeth Robins.
    - Shakespeare, William. Twelfth Night, 1886 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      Arranged by A. Bourchier, W.L. Courtney, 1886.
    - Wallace, William. The Divine Surrender: A Mystery Play (London, 1895) (Box 14, Folder 8)
      A presentation copy.
- Series XIII: Ephemera and Artifacts
  Series XIII is made up of artwork and mementos. It consists of a variety of materials, including watercolors, oil painting, etching, drawings, currency, autographs, leather book jacket, pens, pencils, name plates, a robe and hair.
  - Subseries A: Artifacts
    - See Oversize Material, Box 16, Folders 1-5, 0000
  - Subseries B: Ephemera
    - Leather book jacket with initials "E.R.", 0000 (Box 1)
    - Pens and pencils, 0000 (Box 1)
    - 25 pieces of hair, 0000 (Box 1)
    - Elizabeth Robins stencil plate, 0000 (Box 1)
    - Printing plate for Elizabeth Robins' calling card, 0000 (Box 1)
    - Colonial and Confederate currency, 0000 (Box 1)
      See also Oversize Material, box 17.
    - Autographs (including Thomas Jefferson, James Madison, John Hancock, James Monroe, John Quincy Adams, Millard Fillmore, and Albert of England), 0000 (Box 2)
    - The Boston Weekly Magazine (14 April-18 August 1804) (Box 2)
    - The Connecticut Courant (5 January 1779) (Box 2)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous
    Subseries C is made up of three folders of materials that could not be readily placed.
    - Miscellaneous, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 0000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Oversize - Series II: General Correspondence
  - Subseries A: General Correspondence, 1873-1887
    - Bodine to Winchester (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Subseries B: General Correspondence, 1888-1952
    - Archer, William: Criticism (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Archer, William: Galleys (Box 1, Folder 3)
      This folder of oversized galleys was removed to Fales oversize storage. See Mapcase 2.A.
    - Bell to Buchan, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Gardner (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Pethick-Lawrence to Richmond (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Scott, David: The Watch on the Rhine (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Oversize - Series III: Robins Family Papers
  - Subseries A: Jane H. Robins, 1814-1885
    - Robins, Jane Hussey (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Subseries B: Charles E. Robins, 1836-1893
    - Robins, Charles E.: Little Annie Mining Company Records (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Robins, Charles E.: With the Nuns (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Subseries C: Sarah E. Robins, 1838-1866
    - Robins, Sarah Elizabeth (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Subseries H: Additional Family Members, 1803-1876
    - Additional Family Members (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Additional Family Members: Genealogies (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Oversize - Series IV: Raymond Robins and Margaret Dreier Robins
  - Subseries D: Printed Material and Ephemera
    - Raymond Robins (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Raymond Robins Political Flyers (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Oversize - Series VII: Literary Productions
  - An American Actress at Balmoral (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Below the Salt (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Woman's Secret (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Index (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Possibly to Both Sides of the Curtain
- Oversize - Series VIII: Theater Productions
  - Subseries A: Business Records
    - Acting/Theatre Contracts (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Hedda Gabler: Business Records (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Little Eyolf: Business Records (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Mariana: Business Records (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - The Master Builder: Business Records (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Oversize - Series IX: Photographic Material
  - Subseries A: Elizabeth Robins
    - Elizabeth Robins, #164-170 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Elizabeth Robins, #171-175 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B: General Portraits
    - General Portraits, #413-418 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      Dreiers and Raymond Robins
    - General Portraits, #419 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Forbes-Robertson and ?
  - Subseries C: Robins Family
    - Robins Family, #71-72 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Raymond Robins
    - General Portraits, #420-421 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      George Richmond Parks
  - Subseries D: Alaska
    - Alaska, #422 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Alaska, #423 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Subseries G: Colorado and Other Places
    - Zanesville, Ohio, #81-82 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Old Stone House
    - Zanesville, Ohio, #83-86 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, #87 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Oversize - Series X: Legal and Financial Records
  - Subseries A: Legal Records
    - Elizabeth Robins' Will (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Inventories (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Backsettown Tenancy Agreements (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Subseries B: Financial Records
    - Financial Records--Palace Gate (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Insurance Records (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Oversize - Series XI: Scrapbooks
  - Subseries A: Elizabeth Robins, 1874-1904
    - Scrapbook Material: Elizabeth Robins (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Scrapbook Material: Admiral Guinea/Honesty (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Oversize - Series XII: Printed Material
  - Subseries A: Proofs of Elizabeth Robins' Literary Productions
    - Ancilla's Share, galleys (Box 2, Folder 5)
      formerly Oversize Box 9, folder 1
    - Come and Find Me, galleys (Box 2, Folder 6)
      formerly Oversize Box 9, folder 2
    - Theatre and Friendship, galleys (Box 2, Folder 7)
      formerly Oversize Box 9, folder 3
    - Time is Whispering, galleys (Box 2, Folder 8)
      formerly Oversize Box 9, folder 4
    - Uncle Tom's Cabin (Box 2, Folder 9)
      formerly Oversize Box 9, folder 5
    - The Main Peace Asset; Woman Comes of Age; The Woman Juror (Box 2, Folder 10)
      formerly Oversize Box 9, folder 6
    - A Dark Lantern, page proofs (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Subseries B: Publications by Elizabeth Robins
    - The Frog Baby (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Novel Posters (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Subseries C: Theatre
    - Playbills and announcements of Elizabeth Robins' performances (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Playbills and announcements: Admiral Guinea to Cymbeline (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Playbills and announcements: The Dancing Doll to Fruits of Culture (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Playbills and announcements: Gaity Theatre to Julius Caesar (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Playbills and announcements: King and the Countess to Lyon's Mail (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Playbills and announcements: Ma Cousine to Much Ado About Nothing (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Playbills and announcements: Nancy and Company to The Profligate (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Playbills and announcements: The Queen of Manoa to Sweet Lavender (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Playbills and announcements: The Taming of the Shrew to The Yeomen of the Guard (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Photographs removed from Trilby souvenir program and filed by name of cast member in Series IX.
    - Playbills and announcements: The New Century Theatre (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Criterion interview with Elizabeth Robins, 1898 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Grieg, Edward: Norwegian Bridal Procession (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Subseries D: Literary and Political Publications
    - Literary and Political Productions (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - The Woman's Journal (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Subseries I: Pictures
    - Pictures--Elizabeth Robins, and Others (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Oversize - Series XIII: Ephemera and Artifacts
  - Subseries A: Artifacts
    - Bleacowe, Fanny--Watercolor, 1896 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - [Blilyt?], A.C.--oil of Elizabeth Robins as she appeared in The Trumpet Call (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Browning, Adeline A.--watercolor of Backsettown, ca. 1924 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Includes a letter from Browning dated 1924.
    - Meteyard, T.B.--Japanese Print given to E.R. by I.M. and R. Meteyard, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Paton, Hugh--Etching of London's Tower Bridge, 1906 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Robins, Elizabeth--sketch of a dog, 1881 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Scott, David--watercolor of E.R. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Toroway--drawing, 1826 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - --drawing of William Heinemann as a child (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - --watercolor (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - --drawing of the Ruins of Kenworth Castle (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - --Chinese drawing of birds (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - --shadow portrait of Asabel Hussey (1782-1851), ca. 1804 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - --pencil drawing of Charlotte S. Flintham (Mrs. Ridgely) (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - --pen and ink cartoon depicting (?) William Archer in Scottish dress (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Subseries B: Ephemera
    - Robe and neck velvet (Box 9)
- Mapcase - Series IV: Raymond Robins and Margaret Dreier Robins
  - Subseries D: Printed Material and Ephemera
    Scope and Content
    This folder contains maps and a picture related to Raymond Robins's life in Florida and Alaska.
    - Map of Hernando County, FL (Map-case 2.A, Folder 1)
    - Map of Chinsegut Grounds, FL (Map-case 2.A, Folder 1)
    - Nome Harbor, AK (Map-case 2.A, Folder 1)
- Mapcase - Series XII: Printed Material
  - Subseries C: Theatre
    This folder contains posters and playbills of theatrical productions related to Elizabeth Robins.
    - Admiral Guinea (large) (Map-case 2.A, Folder 2)
    - Admiral Guinea (small) (Map-case 2.A, Folder 2)
    - Grierson's Way (large) (Map-case 2.A, Folder 2)
    - Grierson's Way (small) (Map-case 2.A, Folder 2)
    - Hedda Gabler (with scrapbook) (Map-case 2.A, Folder 2)
    - Industrial Exhibition Entertainments (Map-case 2.A, Folder 2)
    - Ibsen=Uge (Map-case 2.A, Folder 2)
    - Ibsen's Ghost (Map-case 2.A, Folder 2)
    - John Gabriel Borkman (large) (Map-case 2.A, Folder 2)
    - John Gabriel Borkman (small) (Map-case 2.A, Folder 2)
    - Karin (Map-case 2.A, Folder 2)
    - Mariana (Map-case 2.A, Folder 2)
    - Time and Tale (Map-case 2.A, Folder 2)
  - Subseries G: Alaska
    This folder contains maps and charts related to Elizabeth Robins's journeys through Alaska.
    - Arctic Circle, 1949 (Map-case 2.A, Folder 3)
    - Canadian Pacific Railway (Map-case 2.A, Folder 3)
    - Canadian Route to the Yukon (Map-case 2.A, Folder 3)
    - Chilkroot Pass / Town of Dawson (Map-case 2.A, Folder 3)
    - Gold and Coal Fields of Alaska (Map-case 2.A, Folder 3)
    - Rugg's Klondike Gold Fields (Map-case 2.A, Folder 3)
    - Seward Peninsula (Map-case 2.A, Folder 3)
    - US Geological Survey, 1898 (Map-case 2.A, Folder 3)
    - Western Canada (Map-case 2.A, Folder 3)
    - Yukon River and Tributaries (Map-case 2.A, Folder 3)
  - Subseries J: Maps
    Folder 4 contains charts and maps regarding the settlement of the Robins family in Covington, KY and other material related to the Ohio River. Folder 5 contains two fragile maps of Covington, KY. Folder 6 consists of assorted meterological and geographical charts of the United States and Canada.
    - Chart of geographical calculations (KY?) (Map-case 2.A, Folder 4)
    - Geology of Northern Ohio (Map-case 2.A, Folder 4)
    - Lot Plan for the Baptist Education Society land in Covington, KY (Map-case 2.A, Folder 4)
    - Map of planned subdivisions in Covington, KY (Map-case 2.A, Folder 4)
    - Ohio River canal proposal, ~1850 (Map-case 2.A, Folder 4)
    - Plan of the Cincinnati/Convington cemetery (Map-case 2.A, Folder 4)
    - Map of Covington, KY subdivisions (fragile) (Map-case 2.A, Folder 5)
    - Land plot of Backsettown, Essex (Map-case 2.A, Folder 6)
    - Land plot of Illinois College (Map-case 2.A, Folder 6)
    - Map of Canada's natural resources, 1928 (Map-case 2.A, Folder 6)
    - Mexican and American Troops near Matamoros (Map-case 2.A, Folder 6)
    - New York Semi-Weekly Times, Sept 21, 1860 (Map-case 2.A, Folder 6)
    - Northern Hemisphere Wind Chart, 1877 (Map-case 2.A, Folder 6)
    - Ship plans of the Britannic (Map-case 2.A, Folder 6)
    - US War Department Weather Map, 1890 (Map-case 2.A, Folder 6)